const Questions = [
    {
      question: "Which record label did The Notorious B.I.G sign with?",
      answers: {
        a: "Bad Boy Records",
        b: "Death Row Records",
        c: "Sugarhill Records",
        d: "Def Jam Records"
      },
      correctAnswer: "Bad Boy Records"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the lead singer of Green Day?",
      answers: {
        a: "Billie Jean Armstrong",
        b: "Neil Armstrong",
        c: "Billie Joe Armstrong",
        d: "Louis Armstrong"
      },
      correctAnswer: "Billie Joe Armstrong"
    },
    {
      question: "Who wrote the hit 2007 song 'Our Song' for a talent show?",
      answers: {
        a: "Mariah Carey",
        b: "Taylor Swift",
        c: "Beyonce",
        d: "Christina Aguilera"
      },
      correctAnswer: "Taylor Swift"
    },
    {
      question: "Who wrote everyone's moms favorite rap hit 'The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air'?",
      answers: {
        a: "50 Cent",
        b: "Usher",
        c: "Will Smith",
        d: "Eminem"
      },
      correctAnswer: "Will Smith"
    },
    {
      question: "What was the Beatles first single to sell a million copies?",
      answers: {
        a: "Hey Jude",
        b: "Come Together",
        c: "Can't Buy Me Love",
        d: "She Loves You"
      },
      correctAnswer: "She Loves You"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the 2nd studio release by Slipknot?",
      answers: {
        a: ".5, The Gray Chapter",
        b: "Slipknot",
        c: "We Are Not Your Kind",
        d: "Iowa"
      },
      correctAnswer: "Iowa"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the band who wrote the hit single 'Misery Business'?",
      answers: {
        a: "Paramore",
        b: "Alter Bridge",
        c: "Creed",
        d: "Fall Out Boy"
      },
      correctAnswer: "Paramore"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the guitar player in the band 'Guns 'n' Roses'?",
      answers: {
        a: "Ace Frehley",
        b: "Slash",
        c: "Tony Iommi",
        d: "Buckethead"
      },
      correctAnswer: "Slash"
    },
    {
      question: "What year did the album 'Come Whatever May' by Stone Sour release?",
      answers: {
        a: "2001",
        b: "2002",
        c: "2003",
        d: "2004"
      },
      correctAnswer: "2004"
    },
    {
      question: "What band featured the song 'Rollin' as the theme song for WWE's 'The Undertaker' at one point?",
      answers: {
        a: "Static X",
        b: "P.O.D.",
        c: "Limp Bizkit",
        d: "Papa Roach"
      },
      correctAnswer: "Limp Bizkit"
    }
    
  ];